<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Parsed by jbart3h -->
<resources>
     <string name="arrears_sim_v2_notification">Notifications about insufficient balance</string>
     <string name="arrears_sim_v2_summary">Looks like SIM %1$s balance is insufficient. Check SIM %2$s balance and top up to stay connected.</string>
     <string name="arrears_sim_v2_title">"SIM %s couldn't connect to the network"</string>
     <string name="call_recording_disclaimer_msg">"Applicable law in the jurisdiction in which you or other call participants are located may require all parties to consent to recording. You are obliged to comply with such laws, and Xiaomi will not be liable for any illegal use of this feature. Call recordings are only stored on your device and can't be accessed by Xiaomi."</string>
     <string name="call_recording_disclaimer_title">Disclaimer</string>
     <string name="can_not_use">"Can't use"</string>
     <string name="cf_setting_mobile_data_off_alert">Please turn on mobile data</string>
     <string name="cf_setting_network_alert">Please make sure network is available</string>
     <string name="cf_setting_wifi_on_alert">Please turn off Wi-Fi</string>
     <string name="cfu_notification_title">Forward calls</string>
     <string name="config_domain_selection_service_component_name" />
     <string name="config_miui_cpu_model" />
     <string name="depopulated_zone_satellite_notification">Satellite communication reminders</string>
     <string name="disable_cfu_notification_summary">SIM %d is no longer roaming. We recommend turning off call forwarding for this SIM card.</string>
     <string name="enable_cfu_notification_summary">SIM %1$d is roaming. You can forward calls to SIM %2$d to save on roaming charges.</string>
     <string name="enable_esim_summary">Disable SIM %s after turning on</string>
     <string name="enter_mep_esim_manager_title">Manage SIM</string>
     <string name="esos_satellite_string">Test real satellite eSOS mode (Debug Build only)</string>
     <string name="filp_auto_answer_call_title">Unfold to answer calls</string>
     <string name="filp_auto_hangup_call_summary">Works only when Bluetooth or wired earphones are connected</string>
     <string name="filp_auto_hangup_call_title">Fold to end calls</string>
     <string name="fiveg_plus_switch_title">5G+</string>
     <string name="incall_error_carrier_roaming_satellite_mode">You can send and receive messages without a mobile or Wi-Fi network.</string>
     <string name="incall_error_out_of_service_2g">"Mobile network not available.

Connect to a wireless network to make a call.

2G is disabled on this device, which may be impacting your connectivity. Go to Settings and enable Allow 2G to continue."</string>
     <string name="incall_error_out_of_service_wfc_2g_user">"Mobile network is not available.

Connect to a wireless network to make a call.

2G is disabled on this device, which may be impacting your connectivity. Go to Settings and enable Allow 2G to continue."</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_bold_font_family">mipro-bold</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_demibold_font_family">sans-serif-medium</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_extralight_font_family">sans-serif-thin</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_font_family">sans-serif</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_heavy_font_family">sans-serif-black</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_light_font_family">sans-serif-light</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_medium_font_family">sans-serif-medium</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_normal_font_family">sans-serif-light</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_regular_font_family">sans-serif</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_semibold_font_family">mipro-semibold</string>
     <string name="miuix_font_style_misans_thin_font_family">sans-serif-thin</string>
     <string name="mock_carrier_roaming_satellite_string">Mock Carrier Satellite Mode (Debug Build only)</string>
     <string name="msim_select_default_last">Used recently</string>
     <string name="new_arrears_sim_summary">Your SIM card balance may be insufficient or be subject to network restrictions. Contact your carrier for more information.</string>
     <string name="new_arrears_sim_title">"Can't connect to the internet"</string>
     <string name="newcall_settings_summary">5G New Calling services are provided by your carrier</string>
     <string name="newcall_settings_title">5G New Calling</string>
     <string name="no_network_available">Network is not available</string>
     <string name="phone_account_no_config_mobile_networks">The device owner has restricted the ability to change mobile network settings.</string>
     <string name="radio_info_euicc_info">eUICC info:</string>
     <string name="roaming_change_dds_notification">Switch data SIM when roaming</string>
     <string name="roaming_change_dds_notification_text">Your data SIM is roaming. Switch to a local SIM to avoid additional charges.</string>
     <string name="roaming_change_dds_notification_title">Switch data SIM card</string>
     <string name="roaming_preferred_wificall_title">Network preferences (Roaming)</string>
     <string name="sat_Log_Level">Log Level:</string>
     <string name="sat_reg">Reg state:</string>
     <string name="sat_rssi">Rssi:</string>
     <string name="satellite_area_requirement_message">This feature is only available for devices sold on the Chinese mainland (excluding Hong Kong, Macao, and Taiwan), and this feature can only be used on the Chinese mainland (excluding Hong Kong, Macao, and Taiwan).</string>
     <string name="satellite_area_requirement_title">In which regions can this feature be used?</string>
     <string name="satellite_call_indoor_positioning_message">"When a satellite-enabled SIM card isn't installed and you're inside, Xiaomi Science and Technology Park is used as the default location. This allows your device to demonstrate how satellites are located."</string>
     <string name="satellite_call_indoor_positioning_title">"Why is device location shown as Xiaomi Science and Technology Park when I'm indoors?"</string>
     <string name="satellite_call_sound_quality_message">Call quality is related to the strength of the satellite signal. Due to long transmission distance and limited bandwidth, there will be a delay in sending calls and text messages, and audio quality of calls will be worse than that of a regular mobile network.</string>
     <string name="satellite_call_sound_quality_title">Why do satellite calls have poor audio quality and slow speed?</string>
     <string name="satellite_camera_enable_toast">Close Camera before opening Tiantong Satellite communications</string>
     <string name="satellite_ct_business_summary">Services provided by China Telecom</string>
     <string name="satellite_display_insert_support_card_message">To be able to use Tiantong Satellite communications, insert a satellite-enabled SIM card from China Telecom.</string>
     <string name="satellite_display_insert_support_card_title">Insert a satellite-enabled SIM card</string>
     <string name="satellite_display_message">"Looks like your SIM card doesn't support Tiantong Satellite communications. To be able to use this feature, insert a satellite-enabled SIM card from China Telecom. Continue anyway?"</string>
     <string name="satellite_display_search_star">Continue</string>
     <string name="satellite_enable_message">To turn on satellite communication, swipe down to open Control center, turn on the Satellite mode toggle, and follow the instructions to connect. Please note that only China Telecom SIM cards with a Tiantong Satellite subscription support this feature.</string>
     <string name="satellite_enable_title">How do I turn on satellite communication?</string>
     <string name="satellite_environment_requirement_message">"Satellite communication is suitable for areas without terrestrial signal, and we recommend using it only when there is no network available. To avoid signal interference, cases containing metal should be removed before use. Keep a distance of more than %1$dmm between the top of the device and your body or other obstructions during use. This feature will become unavailable when device battery is lower than %2$s, and you won't be able to use it to make calls if device temperature is too high."</string>
     <string name="satellite_environment_requirement_title">What are the environmental requirements for use of this feature?</string>
     <string name="satellite_exit_now_battery">Turn off</string>
     <string name="satellite_feature_introduction">About this feature</string>
     <string name="satellite_handle_connection_failure_message">"Your device will try to connect to the satellite for up to %1$d seconds. If the connection isn't successful within %2$d seconds, a connection timeout will occur. If you receive a prompt that the service hasn't been activated, contact the satellite service operator. Other possible reasons for connection failure include the direct line to the satellite being blocked by tall buildings or other objects directly above or in front of you. In this case, change your location and try again."</string>
     <string name="satellite_handle_connection_failure_title">What do I do if my device has trouble connecting to the satellite?</string>
     <string name="satellite_impact_phone_message">"When Satellite mode is turned on, Wi-Fi, mobile data, and Airplane mode will be turned off and can't be turned on again during use. Location services only support making calls and sending SMS. Features including camera, facial recognition, adding faces for Face unlock, and gaze detection will be unavailable until Satellite mode is turned off. Satellite communication requires a significant amount of power and thus will consume battery power faster than normal use of your device."</string>
     <string name="satellite_impact_phone_title">How will use of satellite communication affect my device?</string>
     <string name="satellite_introduction_title">Tiantong Satellite communications</string>
     <string name="satellite_knew">Got it</string>
     <string name="satellite_low_battery_cancel">Cancel</string>
     <string name="satellite_low_battery_confirm">Turn on</string>
     <string name="satellite_low_battery_message">Battery is too low to turn on Tiantong Satellite communications.</string>
     <string name="satellite_low_battery_super_save_power_message">Battery is low. Turn on Ultra battery saver to use satellite communications normally. Turn on now?</string>
     <string name="satellite_low_battery_title">Low battery</string>
     <string name="satellite_not_show_again">"Don't show again"</string>
     <string name="satellite_notification_text">You can still make calls and send SMS without signal using Tiantong Satellite communications. Turn on this service first.</string>
     <string name="satellite_notification_title">"You're in a weak signal area"</string>
     <string name="satellite_open_tiantong_business_title">Turn on Tiantong Satellite communications</string>
     <string name="satellite_point_title">Turn on Tiantong Satellite communications</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_statement_message">"In order to provide Tiantong Satellite services, we need to access your location and scan for satellites.
After connecting to the satellite, China Telecom needs to access your location in order to locate you in an emergency. For details on how we process your personal information, refer to the "<a href="https://privacy.mi.com/TianTong-dianxin/en_US/">Tiantong Satellite Communications Privacy Statement</a>".
Tap \"Agree\" below to indicate that you have read and agreed to this privacy statement."</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_statement_negative">"Don't agree"</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_statement_positive">Agree</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_statement_title">Privacy statement</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_withdrawal_dialog_enable_negative">Cancel services</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_withdrawal_dialog_message">"If you cancel Tiantong Satellite communications services, we will cease to collect your personal information and delete personal information already collected in accordance with applicable law, unless other laws and regulations specify the retention period of the personal information.
Cancel services now?"</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_withdrawal_dialog_positive">"Don't cancel"</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_withdrawal_dialog_title">Attention</string>
     <string name="satellite_privacy_withdrawal_setting">Cancel Tiantong Satellite communications services</string>
     <string name="satellite_select_enable_sim">Select SIM card</string>
     <string name="satellite_send_receive_sms_message">Once Satellite mode is turned on, you can send and receive SMS. SMS are limited to %d characters, after which they will be split into multiple messages and charged accordingly.</string>
     <string name="satellite_send_receive_sms_title">How do I use satellite communication to send SMS?</string>
     <string name="satellite_signal_boost_setting_summary">Install amplifier to improve signal strength and stability of satellite communications in cloudy and overcast conditions</string>
     <string name="satellite_signal_boost_setting_title">Use Tiantong signal amplifier</string>
     <string name="satellite_signal_boost_toast">Signal amplifier will be turned off when satellite communications are off</string>
     <string name="satellite_start">Got it</string>
     <string name="satellite_start_battery">Got it</string>
     <string name="satellite_thermal_hangup_delay">Device is overheated. Call will end in %ds. Wait for your device to cool down.</string>
     <string name="satellite_use_message">"In areas without regular terrestrial signal, like mountains, deserts, and the ocean, or in areas where ground communications systems have been damaged by natural disasters, your mobile device can connect to satellites to send and receive SMS, make and receive calls, and seek assistance as long as you're in an area where there are no obstructions for %d° to the south."</string>
     <string name="satellite_use_phone_message">"Once Satellite mode is turned on, you can make and receive calls via satellite. Follow the on-screen instructions to ensure call quality and maintain satellite connection during the call. Hands-free will be turned on by default. Stay still and don't change the position of your device during the call to avoid interruptions."</string>
     <string name="satellite_use_phone_title">How do I use satellite communication to make calls?</string>
     <string name="satellite_use_title">Why use satellite communication?</string>
     <string name="satellite_user_reminder">Tiantong Satellite communications need to access your location. Mobile data, camera, and Face unlock will be temporarily unavailable. This feature is only available for satellite-compatible China Telecom SIM cards.</string>
     <string name="select_one_sim_title">Can only use SIM %1$d</string>
     <string name="select_one_sim_title_for_heduohao">Can only use SIM %1$d Sub %2$d</string>
     <string name="select_sim_hint">"Can't use SIM %2$d, while SIM %1$d is in use."</string>
     <string name="select_sim_hint_for_heduohao">"Can't use other, while SIM %1$d Sub %2$d is in use."</string>
     <string name="sim1_description">SIM1</string>
     <string name="sim1_heduohao_card">Sub1</string>
     <string name="sim2_description">SIM2</string>
     <string name="sim2_heduohao_card">Sub2</string>
     <string name="sim3_heduohao_card">Sub3</string>
     <string name="speed_limit_sim_notification">Data speed limits</string>
     <string name="speed_limit_sim_summary">"You've reached your plan's data limit. Data speed will slow down. Contact your carrier for details."</string>
     <string name="speed_limit_sim_title">Data speed is limited</string>
     <string name="start_call_record">Start</string>
     <string name="voice_link_switch_summary">Use data SIM to assist in connecting calls when not connected to the internet</string>
     <string name="voice_link_switch_title">Data-assisted calling</string>
     <string name="wifi_on">Wi-Fi is connected</string>
</resources>
